<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Standing Alone</string>
    <string name="story_welcome_text">Welcome\n\nto Jupiter Artland Treasure\nHunt Adventure</string>

    <string name="preferences_file_key">com.github.hintofbasil.StandingAlone.preferences</string>
    <string name="preferences_locations_found_key">LOCATIONS_FOUND_KEY</string>

    <!-- Introduction -->
    <string name="introduction_1">"<b>Hello</b>\nMy name is Brownie, I am a friendly goblin and I’d like to tell you a story of Jupiter Artland, barely remembered, even by the oldest people."</string>
    <string name="introduction_2">"A long time ago many magical creatures lived in Jupiter Artland. They lived in peace with humans and everyone helped each other. The magical creatures protected people, they took care of the farm animals and  helped out around the farms."</string>
    <string name="introduction_3">"Because of its special location between worlds Jupiter Artland  was one of the few places the creatures could easily travel between a magical dimension in Minecraft and the real world. People were happy to have the creatures as their neighbours."</string>
    <string name="introduction_4">"One day, a terrible flood came and destroyed part of the village and Jupiter Artland. The Creatures and the local people blamed each other. Everyone was scared except Brian, a human from the village who offered to talk to the creatures. Ever since then, Brian is the only person who keeps peace and everyone trusts only him."</string>
    <string name="introduction_5">"I suspect this is not the truth. Why are the other creatures hiding? Why are we stuck in the human dimension? What really happened? Will you help me to find the answers and talk to the other creatures? If you’re ready for the adventure, I am waiting for you next to Suck. See you soon!"</string>
    <string name="introduction_6">"Walk with your device. If you are close enough you will see Brownie, who will tell you what to do next. If you don’t know the location click on the map."</string>

    <!-- Map -->
    <string name="map_description">This is the map of invisible dimention of Jupiter Artland. Find the way to the next location to find Brownie\'s friends, find out what happened and find the treasure! There is a reward waiting for you.. Good luck !</string>
    <string name="map_legend_next">Your next location</string>
    <string name="map_legend_previous">Previous locations</string>
    <string name="enable_location_services_message">Please enable high accuracy location services.  The game may not function correctly without this enabled.</string>
    <string name="enable_location_services_positive">Settings</string>
    <string name="enable_location_services_negative">No thanks</string>
    <string name="location_service_no_data_error">No location\ndata detected.</string>
    <string name="location_service_network_only_error">No GPS\ndata detected.</string>

    <!-- Location Found -->
    <string name="location_found_brownie">"Hello again, thank you so much for helping me. I need to find out what happened, it’s important for me and my friends. The magic gold which allows us to travel between dimensions has disappeared. This mission is not easy because the other creatures are scared of humans.  With your help we will find out the truth but beware, the truth might be scary
We should start with the Stone house. Something tells me one of my friends is hiding there. Let’s find out!"</string>

    <string name="location_found_glaistig">The first creature you found with Brownie was Glaistig, who lived in Stone House. When Asked by Brownie, he mentioned seeing Brian and Blue Witch looking for something with shovels. He advised you to ask Cu Sith, who lives near to The Temple of Apollo. </string>
    <string name="location_found_cu_sith">Cu Sith told you that she talked to Brian about Gold.  The last time she saw him he was with Cailleach Bheur by In Memory.</string>
    <string name="location_found_blue_witch">Cailleach Bheur helped Brian find gold but she doesn\’t know where he hid it.  She thinks you should talk to the Mermaid at Life Mounds.</string>
    <string name="location_found_mermaid">The Mermaid saw Brian looking for Selkie by the bridge on the other side of Life Mounds.</string>
    <string name="location_found_selkie">Selkie thinks you should ask Kelpie by the duck pond.</string>
    <string name="location_found_kelpie">Kelpie saw Brian sneaking around the Crystal Cave (The Light Pours Out of Me).  He thinks Cait Sith had something to do with it.</string>
    <string name="location_found_cait_sith">Cait Sith thinks the gold is somewhere around the Crystal Cave, can you find it?</string>
    <string name="location_found_brian">Oh Hello. Did you think I will just leave the treasure here? Oh no it\’s not that easy!  I was watching you. If you think you\’re so clever, find it yourself! Here\’s a clue. The gold is hidden in a dark room full of trees, not far away from the Steadings. Good luck.</string>
    <string name="location_found_treasure">You found the gold!  Take this screen and show it at the shop.</string>

</resources>
