<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Standing Alone</string>
    <string name="story_welcome_text">Welcome\n\nto Jupiter Artland Treasure\nHunt Adventure</string>

    <string name="preferences_file_key">com.github.hintofbasil.StandingAlone.preferences</string>
    <string name="preferences_locations_found_key">LOCATIONS_FOUND_KEY</string>

    <!-- Introduction -->
    <string name="introduction_1"><b>Hello</b>\n\nMy name is Brownie. I am a goblin. Let me tell you a story of Jupiter Artland.</string>
    <string name="introduction_2">A long time ago many magical creatures lived here. They were helping and protecting people.</string>
    <string name="introduction_3">They came from a magical dimention called Minecraft, where everything is almost the same but square.</string>
    <string name="introduction_4">One day, a terrible flood destroyed Jupiter Artland. Everyone was blamed creatures. Only Brian, one of humans keeped peace. Ever since then everyone trusts only him..</string>
    <string name="introduction_5">I suspect Brian is hidding something. Help me to find out the truth. Find me next to the Suck to start our adventure. Use the map if you don\'t know the way.\n<b>See you soon!</b></string>

    <!-- Map -->
    <string name="map_description">This is the map of invisible dimention of Jupiter Artland. Find the way to the next location to find Brownie\'s friends, find out what happened and find the treasure! There is a reward waiting for you.. Good luck !</string>
    <string name="map_legend_next">Your next location</string>
    <string name="map_legend_previous">Previous locations</string>

    <!-- Location Found -->
    <string name="location_found_glaistig">That\'s Glaistig! She is suprised to see humans. Also, She is upset becasue she stuck in Minecraft dimention like others.\n\nGlaistig is saying that has seen Brian and Blue Witch looking for something. We need to find his friend Cu Sith at the Temple of Apollo to find out more..</string>

</resources>
